Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/zakariahadadia (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Coaching
Executive Search
Event Planning

Zakaria Hadadia

Make your own McKinsey!

Tokyo, Tokyo, Japan

Summary

Hiring Bilingual Talent for our McKinsey Japan office!

If you are an experienced professional that is considering taking a step into the consulting world don't hesitate to reach out to me. At McKinsey we are still growing our teams of professionals across all industries.

Experience

McKinsey & Company

3 years 3 months

Lead Recruiter

November 2023 - Present (1 year 8 months)

Tokyo, Japan

Senior Recruiter

April 2022 - November 2023 (1 year 8 months)

Tokyo, Japan

- Leading experienced professionals recruiting team
- Recruiting Bilingual talent for our Japan offices
- Collaborating with local & global teams
- Project managing
- Learning and development

Wolt

Talent Acquisition Partner
July 2020 - April 2022 (1 year 10 months)

- Recruiting for Japan Market: Kyushu, Kanto, Hokkaido, Tohoku, Okinawa region
- Building teams in new offices
- Building New Grad programs and Internships
- Collaborating on Talent marketing strategies with Marketing and Talent Marketing teams

Robert Walters 2 years

Associate Consultant 2019 - June 2020 (1 year)

Within 23 wards, Tokyo, Japan

Recruitment Researcher 2018 - May 2019 (1 year)

Tokyo, Japan

Scania Parts Logistics
Returns
October 2010 - February 2015 (4 years 5 months)
Belgium, Opglabbeek

Education

Ritsumeikan Asia Pacific University
International Management, Strategic Management &
Organization · (2015 - 2019)